<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://simonaustin.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:53:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://simonaustin.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mark Wright</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/mark-wright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:53:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/mark-wright/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my time at BlackBerry, Simon was pivotal to the development of Blackerry&amp;rsquo;s marketing analytics practice; his deep digital measurement expertise in combination with his exceptional lateral-thinking skills were invaluable in developing a clearer understanding of mROI and, in turn, the attitudes, actions, and opinions of BlackBerry customers and prospects. I recommend Simon without reservation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Bailetti</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/marco-bailetti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:50:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/marco-bailetti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Simon is a smart analytics strategiest AND practitioner. People like Simon have helped shaped the Analytics industry to what it is today, driven by a passion for &amp;lsquo;data-driven insights&amp;rsquo; and business optimization. Simon is a great partner to work with. He spends the time to listen, and understand different point of view, and always makes decisions based on what is best for the business, and ultimately, the customer. I would work with Simon anytime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Berry</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/chris-berry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:30:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/testimonial/chris-berry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The state of Canadian digital analytics is better off because of Simon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simon, at BlackBerry, is responsible for a non-trivial percentage of overall analytical spending in Canada. And not just for a year. But over a sustained, persistent, period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;His influence extends from Kitchener-Waterloo all the way to Spadina and Adelaide streets in Toronto, and will often spillover into New York and Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simon works with a very heterogeneous audience within BlackBerry, ranging from executives who want the bullet points, directors looking to build solid business cases, and some of the smartest managers looking for exploitable market cleavages. He has effectively managed an orchestra of solid lines, dotted lines, sustainably, for several years. BlackBerry is better off because of his steady hand within digital analytics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Director, Public Web</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-product/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;took-over-ownership-of-sun-life-website&#34;&gt;Took over ownership of Sun Life website&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After my success optimizing the site, I fully took over the public facing website, adding agile development and publishing teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team size is about 30 FTE&amp;rsquo;s across the Agile dev team, SEO content team, personalization team, and publishing team where I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to set them up so I manage a team of teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My role involves defining the technical vision, strategy, and multi-year roadmap for the Public Web. I work closely with UX, Marketing, and IT architecture teams to create innovative, user-friendly experiences that meet both customer needs and business goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director, Digital Optimization</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-optimization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;took-a-role-to-optimize-for-impact--driving-growth-and-breaking-barriers&#34;&gt;Took a role to optimize for impact.  Driving growth and breaking barriers.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve had the privilege of owning SEO, SEM and Digital Optimization for Sun Life Canada, leading a small but agile optimization team that could rapidly test ideas using Adobe Target and the expertise of our in-house designers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of my proudest achievements was driving a 40% increase in advisor sales from our primary digital channel. This came through deep data analysis, rethinking media spend, and making significant process improvements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director, Real Time Decision Engine</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-decision-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/sunlife-decision-engine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;moved-to-sun-life-to-take-on-ambitious-project-to-build-the-future-for-them-scaling-real-time-personalization-across-channels&#34;&gt;Moved to Sun Life to take on ambitious project to build the future for them, scaling real-time personalization across channels&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a good run at BlackBerry I decided it was time to try something new.  I had a decision to make between going to Accenture and Sun Life.  I chose Sun Life because the role was interesting, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be on the road 75% and away from my young family.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Manager, Marketing Automation &amp; Analytics</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/blackberry-marketing-automation-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/blackberry-marketing-automation-copy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;during-a-downturn-opportunities-to-gain-skills&#34;&gt;During a downturn, opportunities to gain skills&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I continued leading all aspects of Digital Analytics but took on additional responsibilities as teams were laid off, including the technical leadership of Consumer and Enterprise CRM at BlackBerry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of my key projects was globally integrating the Eloqua system with Salesforce (SFDC), which helped streamline processes and improve efficiency as BlackBerry shifted focus from B2B2C to B2B. I also managed ExactTarget/Salesforce Marketing Cloud for our remaining B2C emails, ensuring our tools and systems were optimized for success.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analytics Analyst → Analytics Manager</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/blackberry-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/blackberry-analytics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;back-to-canada-and-working-for-a-tech-company&#34;&gt;Back to Canada, and working for a tech company&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Working at Deluxe paid well, and my e-commerce team was thriving. However, the teams around me were struggling with layoffs and downsizing. Sensing it might be time for a change, I started looking for my next opportunity and almost immediately, I got a call from BlackBerry with an offer to relocate me back to Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This was BlackBerry before the iPhone era—a company at its peak and an incredible place to work. The pace was fast, and the pressure was high, but it was exhilarating. I was brought on to lead digital analytics, focusing on measuring website performance and evaluating the effectiveness of digital marketing campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Analyst</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/deluxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/deluxe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;using-my-skills-to-make-a-living-wage&#34;&gt;Using my skills to make a living wage&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking back at my time at Openflows, it’s almost unbelievable how poorly I was paid—something that might be hard to imagine for today’s graduates. More than once considered taking up manual labor in construction, even temporarily, because it paid better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By 2005, the job market for technical roles was starting to improve, and I landed a position with the Canadian office of Deluxe Corporation in Midland, Ontario, as a Database Analyst. After quickly mastering their analytics systems, I was tasked with hiring a Digital Analyst for their U.S. office in Groton, MA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://simonaustin.net/experience/openflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://simonaustin.net/experience/openflows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;laying-the-foundation-forced-to-hustle&#34;&gt;Laying the Foundation: Forced to hustle&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I graduated university just as the dot-com bubble of the early 2000s was fully deflating. Like most of my graduating class, my full-time job offer—secured after a co-op role doing C/C++ development for a desktop application—vanished overnight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Determined to keep moving forward, I took on whatever small local jobs I could find. If a project required a programming language I didn’t know, I learned it. Need someone to manage a *nix system? I was there. A database to set up or analyze? I’d handle that too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
